Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Animation Number 4
Love
Single kanji A
Love takes away without reservation
Animation Number 4
Blue Scene
Animation Number 'none'
But...
Animation Number 8
But, humyan.
My myaster loves you.
Solemn
Yellow Scene
Animation Number 'none'
There are people for whom it's impossible.
Animation Number 10
Animation Number 14
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
So if you fall in love with my myaster, I think that might bottle me up.
Quit joking. Even I'm not gonna fall for that one.
Plus, it's just terrible.
In this world, there are good lies and bad lies, and-
You really are stupid, humyan. Do you think I'm clever enough to lie to you?
But, cat. If that's not a lie...
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
Aren't you just mistaken?
There's no way she could be in love with me.
Why do you think that? I wouldn't understand my myaster.
She's the only my myaster I have.
But-
But even though she loves you, you're going out with someone else.
Animation Number 25
Restraint / Anger / Accumulation
And showing it off in front of her.
Documentary
Animation Number 31
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
But Hanekawa isn't acting like that!
Headache didn't stop at all
Animation Number 33
If anything, she wants me to be with Senjougahara! She's even given me advice-
It was getting just worse
Animation Number 36
That's exactly what has her so stressed, meow!
Animation Number 38
Disorder
Single kanji B
I feel... bad.
Animation Number 36
Do you think a girl like my myaster could work up the guts to ask you out?
What have I done?
Animation Number 41
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
She couldn't even let slip a single hint of it.
I don't know everything, I-
But, I had no way to tell that... If Hanekawa...
Animation Number 48
If that girl decided to hide her true feelings,
even Senjougahara wouldn't be able to figure her out
Animation Number 51
Documentary
Pressure
Single kanji C
But...
Animation Number 51
Am I... insensitive?
Animation Number 52
Then that talk about the future course...
Although partly due to Oshino's influence,
you can say that was Hanekawa Tsubasa's
grand journey of broken heart...
Then that talk about the future course...
Although partly due to Oshino's influence,
you can say that was Hanekawa Tsubasa's
grand journey of broken heart...
And she had headache too,
right after that career talk.
Animation Number 54
And,
Animation Number 56
Documentary
That time she closed her eyes and tried to kiss me...
Animation Number 58
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Wow, Hanekawa was-
Nisio Isin
Episode 15
Bakemono
gatari
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Typeface used for images: HGP mincho B
Tsubasa Cat, Part Five
Episode 15
Animation Number 62
Kawa
Single kanji D
Animation Number 62
Kawa
Single kanji D
Hanekawa Tsubasa is a very important person for me
Animation Number 62
Last Episode
How long?
How long has Hanekawa loved me?
Animation Number 68
Obey
Single kanji E
Spring break
Animation Number 88
Since spring break.
REMINISCENCE
From episode 1, animation number 25
I guess my myaster thought the humyan/vyampire relationship thing was the purrfect thing
REMINISCENCE
From episode 1, animation number 54
From episode 1, animation number 59
to break her free from the life she was sick of.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That's-
But she never would have expected a rival to appear, meow.
Meanwhile, the girl you're going out with moved in lightning-fast.
REMINISCENCE
From episode 5, animation number 233
Purple Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That time, Hanekawa...
Animation Number 80
Was happy for me.
That's what I thought
Animation Number 82
But...
Animation Number 83
Was that a lie too?
Animation Number 84
Animation Number 86
I never lie.
I never lie
Wrong.
If this is true, you've told nothing but lies, Hanekawa Tsubasa!
Following, a performance of troupe Dog Curry
Animation Number 93
A girl raised in a cold, unloving family.
During her spring break,
she has a shocking encounter with a supernyatural entity who happens to be a classmate.
It feels like fate. Her heart begins to stir.
Then, later, he saves her life-she's convinced that it's love.
Or something.
End of performance
Animation Number 94
Whether she's right or wrong, she feels like she's had something purrecious snatched away from her.
Wait, cat. There's something not quite right there.
Even if I'm the source of her stress like you're saying, that wouldn't be enough to release you.
There must be something else big that's stressing her out.
Wrong. It's all you.
But aren't you the embodiment of all the stress Hanekawa built up from her home life?
Just a couple months of love shouldn't-
"Just"?
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
And just what makes you think a few months of lovesickness
Embryo
Animation Number 109
29th day
can't be worse than over a decade of family problems, meow?
Back to the belly
Animation Number 113
What, haven't you ever really fallen for anyone?
Are you just dating that girl to shut her up?
You may as well dump her and get with my myaster, then.
I can't do that, cat.
Oh? Why not? Don't you need to reward my myaster for everything she's done for you?
If I did that, Hanekawa would just be taking advantage of my debt to her.
I don't want to let her do that kind of thing.
No, that's not it. That's just a convenient excuse.
I can't deny my feelings for Senjougahara.
I figured you'd go for Hanekawa-san between the two of them.
REMINISCENCE
New footage for episode 15, animation number 130.
Animation Number 131
Connection
Single kanji F
You are wrong, Hachikuji
Animation Number 131
Even with how she acts sometimes, I still love Senjougahara.
Yes
Animation Number 135
I love everything
There's nothing I don't love about her
Animation Number 135
She's the first woman I've ever really loved.
Oh, is that so?
Plus, cat.
No matter the circumstances, it's Hanekawa's own weakness that brought you forth.
Denial/Voice/Line
Animation Number 144
What you told me is something Hanekawa should have told me herself.
She's just forcing you to do the hard part.
Denial/Voice/Line
Animation Number 147
There are plenty of people who've lived through the same problems Hanekawa is having
without relying on an aberration.
Her just relying on you is an insult to each one of them.
Denial/Voice/Line
Animation Number 148
You've got some nerve to say that, meow. Oh well, I guess you've earned the right.
After all, you're the guy so kindhearted he'd even sacrifice himself to save a mortally-wounded vyampire.
REMINISCENCE
From episode 1, animation number 20
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
If you're kind to everyone, that means no humyan is special.
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
Animation Number 158
I understand that because my myaster was kind to everyone, too.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Oh well, there's no changing someone's feelings.
I learned that last time. Learned it quite well, meow.
That's good.
I guess Hanekawa feels the same way, then?
Then I might have been a bit harsh scolding her like that.
What do you mean?
Well... Vampires have a special charisma, right?
And because of it I've been popular with the girls since spring break. Hanekawa told me that.
Hanekawa's always so serious. If she's so caught up in her feelings, she must  have been a victim of that.
Wait, why did you stop talking?
No, you're wrong.
A knockoff vyampire like you can't use his charismya at all.
But...
The power of charismya isn't a love potion like that, anyway.
It's the power to completely remove their will, purroducing nothing more than your very own marionette.
Marionette?
Not just infatuate them?
Well, just think, humyan. Are any of the girls you know what you'd call "completely obedient"?
Is there anyone who'll do anything you say, with no questions asked?
Crab
Snail
Monkey
Snake
Cat
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Not a one.
Then...
Sorry, I'm just teasing.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That must have been-
Was that a lie?
Animation Number 190
A lie better kept unsaid
A painful wish
Animation Number 191
There's no changing someone's feelings.
But that's not like my myaster at all.
I guess I gave it away by being too dumb to lie, meow.
Maybe that's another hard part she forced you to do.
I guess I should be proud that Hanekawa loves me.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Anyway, we need to find Shinobu.
Now that I think of it, no one I asked to help has gotten back to me yet.
I should probably tell Sengoku to call it off soon.
Hey, humyan.
There's one other way.
A way to confine me again without relying on a vyampire.
How?
Why don't you walk on over to that streetlight?
Like this?
A little bit further, meow. You're right under it, so you don't have enough of a shadow there.
Shadow?
Tsubasa Cat Ep 5
A beginning
Animation Number 255
Documentary
Spirit
Cat, you-
Solemn
I told you I didn't just come here to make friends.
I'm not pathetic enough yet to want to be friendly with a human.
What do you think this will accomplish?!
I told you I had another plan, meow.
I don't need to be here if the source of her stress-you-is gone.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That's-
Haven't you learned?!
When you attacked Hanekawa's parents during Golden Week...
Just doing that won't solve anything!
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
You didn't go away! You started attacking passersby!
REMINISCENCE
From episode 11, animation number 263
Human stress isn't that simple!
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I failed that time. I didn't kill her parents, meow.
I've learned. I won't make the same mistake twice.
I will certainly kill you.
Kill
Animation Number 260
I will certainly kill you
CERTAINLY KILL
Animation Number 260
Kill...
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
But that's Hanekawa's inner thoughts.
Hanekawa's words.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I owe Hanekawa my life. I'd do anything for her.
You should be happy. You get to ride my myaster's naughty body straight to Heaven.
I'm dying for Hanekawa's sake.
Hitagi
Animation Number 272
No! I can't!
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
If Hanekawa kills me, Senjougahara will kill her for sure!
So I can't die!
That's the absolute worst way to handle it!
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Let me go!
Just let me go!
Pleading for your life?
Very well. If you promise you'll be my myaster's lover, I'll let you go.
I told you, I can't!
You sure did.
Well, then.
Die.
Or maybe you could try calling for someone to help?
You've helped plenty of people, maybe one of them will return the favor.
One of them...
Mayoi
Animation Number 299
No one's going to save me.
No one? Why?
People just accept help selfishly, for their own sake.
You don't really think that, do you?
It's just something you say.
It's not how you feel, meow.
The question's how you really feel.
Suruga
Animation Number 306
Maybe people do just accept help selfishly for their own sake-
but what does that have to do with the reasons their helper has?
Animation Number 308
Nadeko
How many people do you think want to help you?
Are you rejecting every one of them?
They'd be sad, wouldn't they.
Hanekawa and Senjougahara...
Kanbaru and Sengoku, too.
Circles
on water
Animation Number 315
Even Hachikuji.
For example, if I died
Animation Number 315
If I...
Save... me...
Save me...
Shinobu!
Animation Number 320
Yellow Scene
Animation Number 'none'
You don't have enough of a shadow there.
Black Hanekawa/Reminiscence/Voice-only
Animation Number 343
That's enough! Stop, Shinobu!
If you go any further, you'll kill Hanekawa too. I don't want that.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Araragi-kun...
Don't say lonely things like, "I care more about my debt to you than our friendship."
Be nice, Araragi-kun.
Okay.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Come on, onii-chan, it's morning!
You need to get up!
Come on !
After that, Kanbaru, who had come to check up on us, helped me and Hanekawa home.
And that day, before school, I went to the ruined cram school.
To bring Shinobu, still hidden in my shadow, back to Oshino.
But...
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
GRAND CULTURAL FESTIVAL
You're late.
I had to stop for something.
How are you feeling?
Great.
Good morning.
I don't know yet how much Hanekawa remembers.
I need to ask her someday, but not now.
Hanekawa needs time to mend her heart, too.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Hitagi
Animation Number 432
Welcome back.
I'm back.
You get to plan our next date.
If you bring me somewhere weird, I'll flay you.
Sure.
I'm cool with that.
This time, I'll show you my treasure.
Someday even crabs need to start on a journey.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I had Kanbaru wait for us, and after school she,
Senjougahara, Hanekawa, and I went back to the ruined cram school.
One day, I'll leave this city.
Now I understand.
When I came here yesterday...
Oshino was outside getting ready to move on.
I won't just disappear without telling you.
I'm an adult, so I at least know to do that.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Why didn't I realize?
That line itself just had to have been a farewell.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
He's the kind of person who never says goodbye.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That awkward man who hates farewells more than anything...
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
It shows just how deeply he cared about me.
Koyomi/Monologue/Line
Animation Number 475
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
When I went searching for for Shinobu, he let the meddlecat free on purpose, and left this place behind.
Because he believed I could handle Shinobu and Hanekawa myself.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Man, he really was.
Yeah, he was.
Definitely.
He sure was.
A nice guy.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I may meet more aberrations in the future.
But that's okay.
Now I know.
There's dark places in this world, and things that live in them.
Even within my own shadow.
The culture festival finally starts tomorrow.
Our class project is-
a haunted house.
Tsubasa Cat, Part Five
Cat
Bakemonogatari
With that...
End
That's Deneb, Altair, Vega
are ga DENEBU ARUTAIRU BEGA
the summer triangle that you pointed out.
kimi wa yubisasu natsu no daisankaku
So remember
oboete
to look at the sky.
sora wo miru
I finally found you, Altair,
yatto mitsuketa orihimesama
though where are you, Vega?
dakedo doko darou hikoboshisama
This is loneliness.
kore ja hitoribocchi
I looked up from the pitch-dark world.
makkura no sekai kara miageta
The stars fell in the night sky, and
yozora wa hoshi ga furu you de
just when was it from?
itsu kara darou
That I, who ran after you,
kimi no koto wo
was there.
oikakeru watashi ga ita
Please heed my wish.
douka onegai
Don't be surprised.
odorokanaide
Listen
kiite yo
to these feelings
watashi no
of mine.
kono omoi wo