Se-no
One, two!
Demo sonnan ja dame
But that's no good.
Mou sonna ja hora
Look, with that,
Kokoro wa shinka suru yo motto motto
my heart is evolving more and more.
Kotoba ni sureba kiechau kankei
If the relationship will disappear when we put
nara kotoba wo keseba ii ya tte
we put it into words, we should just do away
Omotteta osoreteta dakedo are?
I thought this, and I was afraid, but what is this?
nanka chigau ka mo
I think something is different, somehow.
Senri no michi mo ippo kara
Even the longest path starts with one step
ishi no you ni katai sonna ishi de
so I'll make my resolve as hard as stone.
chiri mo tsumoreba yamato nadeshiko?
Many little things add to Yamato Nadeshiko?
shii nuki de iya shinu ki de
Selflessly, no, recklessly.
Fuwafuwari fuwafuwaru anata ga namae
Softly, gently, with just you calling my name, I float up into space.
wo yobu sore dake de chuu e ukabu
Fuwafuwaru fuwafuwari anata ga watte
Gently, softly, with just your laugh, a smile comes to my face.
iru sore dake de egao ni naru
Kami-sama arigatou unmei no itazura demo
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate.
Meguriaeta koto ga shiawase na no
I'm happy that I could meet you.
Demo sonnan ja dame
But that's no good.
Mou sonna ja hora
Look, with that,
Kokoro wa shinka suru yo motto motto
my heart is evolving more and more.
Sou sonnan ja iya da
Right, we can't have that.
Nee sonna ja mada
Hey, that'll come later.
Watashi no koto mitete ne zutto zutto
Look at me, okay? Always, always.