koishikute
You’re dear to me;
itoshikute
I long for you;
tomaranai
I can’t stop.
semete kono kokoro wa
At least this heart of mine
kimi no moto e
Will go to where you are.
Passionless observer
kimi ga omou hodo
I’m not as much of an angel
Passionless observer
Painfully well accustomed
tenshi ja nai kara
As you think I am.
Painfully well accustomed
Fading memories
kirameku kimochi wa
These shining feelings
chimimouryou
Are really evil spirits.
Spirits
Spirits of mountains
Spirits of mountains and streams
Ever faithful and devoted
isso no koto mou
At this point, I may as well.
Ever faithful and devoted
Tear out the root
akuma ni naretara
What if I become a demon?
Tear out the root
Calmly, with open heart
tsubuyaku kotoba wa
The whispered words
Calmly, with open heart
imi mourou
Have a hazy meaning.
Mean
Meaning
Meaning unclear
ano hi no mama de zutto matteru
Just like I did on that day, I keep on waiting.
akirameta mama ima mo matteru no
I’ve given up, and I’m waiting even now.
iitakute
I want to say it;
ienakute
I can’t say it;
todokanai
It won’t reach,
Yellow Scene
Animation Number 'none'
konna soba ni ite mo
Even though I’m so close to you.
Blue Scene
Animation Number 'none'
nee dou sureba ii no
Hey, what should I do?
koishikute
You’re dear to me;
itoshikute
I long for you;
tomaranai
I can’t stop.
semete kono kokoro wa
At least this heart of mine
kimi no moto e
Will go to where you are.
Sense of smell
Very sharp
Personality
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE