muishiki no uchi ni
The scenery I caught while I was unconscious
toraeta sono keshiki wa
zutto machi nozonde ita
Isn't the future I've always been waiting for.
mirai ja naku
watashi no shiranai
Seeing the smile I don't know and haven't seen before,
mita koto mo nai egao
kugitsuke ni natte mama
I stood still, as though stapled to the spot.
tachitsukushita
tenten barabara
Scattered in droplets, the two worlds stray from each other.
futatsu no sekai hagureteku
zenzen barabara mujun shite iru omoi
Completely scattered, I can't control my ambivalent feelings.
osaekirenaku naru
gamushara na kokoro de
With my reckless heart,
I'll move forward and leap over you someday.
itsu no hi ka anata o tobikoshite
mae e susume
yamikumo na kokoro ga
Before I knew it, my clouded heart passed me by,
itsu no ma ni watashi o oikoshite
kara matta kimochi
and my feelings were tangled.
hashire hashire
Run, run! It's the one thing I can always do.
itsumo dekiru koto wa hitotsu
hayaku hayaku hayaku
Quickly, quickly, quickly, to that other side!
sono mukou e