Back to the lunch break
Animation Number 1A
We're going on a date.
What?
Uh... what?
Say, "Aah."
Whoa, what's this?!
This kind of lovey dovey event between lovey dovey lovers is something you'd see in a manga!
What's with this! I'm not happy at all. I don't want this. In fact, it's just scary!
What's wrong, Araragi-kun?
I said, say "Aah."
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
A-Aah...
Gotcha.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I'm happy to see that you're smiling...
Araragi-kun, there's some rice on your cheek.
You put it there.
I'll take it off for you.
All right, all gone.
Thrown away.
Animation Number 37
Well then, we're going on a date.
No... that's not what I mean.
A date...
Could you... go on a date with me?
How about... we go... on a date?
What, are you against it, Araragi-kun?
Well... I'm not against it.
Okay, then go on a date with me, Araragi-kun.
So it ultimately comes down to that.
Do you have any complaints... rather, any questions?
None.
Okay.
Then after school I'll make some excuse to go home early and get ready, so...
Araragi-kun, come to my house once you're done preparing for the cultural festival.
All right!
That's how today, June 13th, would come to be celebrated as the day I went on my first date with my girlfriend...
Animation Number 59
or so I thought.
Animation Number 67
ima nara mada ma ni au kara
I can still yet make it on time,
tekkai shita hou ga ii yo
so I might as well get out.
motto kanchigai shiteshimau mae ni
Before I'm even more wrong.
staple stable
kimi wo tojita kotoba no hari
The staples of the words that bound you
itsu no ma ni ka
Just when was it that you
kono mune ni sasatte shimatteita
pierced this heart of mine?
itai
It hurts
kimi no sei da na
I guess it was your fault
konaide, konna konna watashi wo
Don't come, near me.
minaide, sonna sonna toko made
Don't look, to that, that place
hanasanaide, anna anna egao de
Don't talk, with that, that smiling face
donna, dare ni mo,
Whatever, with whomever,
doko made de mo tsuzuku
I'll continue on anywhere
kono sora no you na
in this sky
owari no nai eien mo chikatte
like an eternity
ijiwaru de yasashi sono umi no you na
without an end, I vow
kokoro ni tobikondara uketomete
When I leap into your heart, I take it
omosa ja
Harsh and kind, like that ocean
hakarenai konna omoi
It's heavy
kimi dake ni ima
These kinds of feelings you cannot weigh
tsutaeru kara
Because I can only tell it to you now.
At least
I understood one thing clearly.
Senjougahara Hitagi.......
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Although she might be extremely clever and unusually calculating,
when it comes to matters of love,
her battle power is zero.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Certainly zero.
Even on that Mother's day, when we started dating,
it was obvious that she was reckless like an RPG hero
who enters a cave without a torch.
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
Does she think it is necessary to use this methodology
similar to aggressive diplomacy, just like showing all your cards
and relying on the decision of the opponent,
when delicate love affairs are concerned?
She also has no head for others' feelings.
Under such pressure, 99 men out of 100 would definitely back out.
It's scary. Even I understand it though I have no experience in love.
Well
If she bases her strategy on the fact
that I am that single man remaining out of those 100,
then I'll tip my hat to that.
This is bad.
I'm infatuated.
I can't even joke about it.
To tell the truth, at this rate I want
to succumb to passion and embrace Senjougahara.
It's pretty obvious that I'll lose her after this.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
I didn't have a lot of cards to begin with.
That's why this kind of relationship
for now seemed okay to me.
Not that I didn't want to advance.
Treasure
Sleep
Lying together gazing at the stars in the sky.
It's enough for us to be lovers like that.
Typeface used for images: HGP mincho B
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
Episode 12
I talked a bit too long with Sengoku
and Hanekawa at the school gates...
Animation Number 65
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Maybe I'm a bit late...
You're earlier than I expected.
Oh well.
Well then, we're going.
Follow me.
H-Hey...
What's wrong, Araragi-kun?
You're pretty quiet.
Hey, do you understand the situation we're in right now?
I don't.
Now
Animation Number 76
When is "now"?
How are you spelling "situation"?
Situation
Animation Number 77
That's not where context comes from?!
My girlfriend's father is with us on our first date... This isn't a date; it's torture.
What exactly was I celebrating?!
I knew you'd be nervous, Araragi-kun, since this is our first date,
but you won't make it at this rate. The night is long.
Yeah...
I'm not nervous because this is my first date!
Hitagi's line / Chat
Animation Number 84
Hey, Araragi-kun.
Do you... love me?
Answer me. Do you... love me?
What's this, you won't answer me? Could it be that you don't love me, Araragi-kun?
I-I love you.
I see. I love you too, Araragi-kun.
Thank you... very much...
It's nothing.
Araragi-kun, you really are quiet.
You're being unusually taciturn. Normally you chat with me more.
Could it be that you're in a bad mood today?
It has nothing to do with my mood...
Ah, so your head is sluggish.
You're taking advantage of my confusion to say whatever you want!
Araragi-kun, your jabs are always
energetic, even when other things aren't.
All right, then I'll be nice and give you a topic.
You can just answer, Araragi-kun.
What do you like about me?
The parts I don't like are obvious!
Damn it!
I was seriously looking forward to this! It was like a dream come true!
A dream? That's going overboard.
Did you know, Araragi-kun?
When you look up the words "Vain"
and "Person"... oh, what was it again?
Man
Animation Number 111
Fickle
Animation Number 112
Araragi
Animation Number 114
It's probably me.
A new kanji was born
Animation Number 115
Hey, Senjougahara, seriously, what are you planning?
Senjougahara?
Could you be referring to me, or was that directed at Father?
Father, Araragi-kun is addressing you.
Hitagi-san! I was addressing Hitagi-san!
The "calling her by her given name" event
Animation Number 119
What is it, Araragi-kun?
So you won't use my first name. Not that I care.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
So, Hitagi-san...
I'm going to take the liberty of asking you again, but what are you planning? What are you scheming?
I'm not scheming anything.
Anyway, Araragi-kun,
there's a famous mystery author by the name of Kuriowa Ruiko, but if you break up the characters in her name,
Ruiko Kuroiwa
Animation Number 111
Wicked
Animation Number 124
it becomes "Wicked Bad Child."
Bad
Animation Number 125
Child
Animation Number 126
Do you think that was intentional?
I don't care about something like that!
Wicked child
Animation Number 128
Wicked child and bad child are both referring to you!
Bad child
Animation Number 129
You sure say cruel things in front of my parent.
Father, it seems your child is a wicked child and a bad child.
Oh, you got quiet again. I guess I teased you a bit too much.
Araragi-kun, you react so easily that I only want to depress you more.
Those words just depressed me the most.
So what parts do you like about me?
Animation Number 140
That you're nice,
you're cute,
Animation Number 140
and you come to my rescue, like a prince, whenever I'm in trouble.
Everything I said before was my fault!
Speaking of trash, I mean Araragi-kun...
Were you about to call your boyfriend "trash" right there?
What are you saying? Don't accuse me of something I wouldn't do.
Anyway Araragi-kun, how did you do on the last test?
Remember, I took care of you day and night at my house, just the two of us?
Why would you intentionally say it like that?
So? How was it?
Yeah, I scored better than expected.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I even got a better score in math, which was supposed to be my best subject.
It's all thanks to your help. Thank you, Senjougahara.
Father? It seems that Araragi-kun wants to thank you, so could you listen to him?
Thank you Hitagi-san!
It would've been better if we could've gone over the answers right after the test.
Well, asking that much of you at
this point is a bit too demanding, isn't it?
Though it's a little ironic to say this, since I was the one who tutored you, I'm a little surprised.
Is it surprising?
Yes, considering it's you, it wasn't very amusing or anything.
I didn't get tutored by you to get laughs, you know.
I was really looking forward to a situation like, "I studied so hard, but my scores were actually worse than usual!"
In some ways, I'm disappointed.
Asking for something like that is much more demanding!
Araragi's line (capricious)
Oh really?
But it's really amazing. I compliment you.
At this rate, you might be able to do even better, Araragi-kun.
Better, you say?
If you'd like, it's fine with me if I tutor you from now on.
That's...
the best deal possible.
Oh really?
Then every day from now on, you will come to my house for tutoring.
E-Every day?! Do smart people really study that much?
No, obviously this program is designed for you, Araragi-kun.
Smart people are smart before they even start studying.
It seems like Hanekawa studies every day, though.
Araragi-kun, the "studying" that Hanekawa-san does,
unfortunately, is on a completely different level than our "studying."
Hanekawa-san is the real thing. She's from a different world than us.
But it's not like Hanekawa always aces tests, right?
If Hanekawa-san can't score 100, then the problem is with the test. I wonder what that's like, though.
When I think about how much pressure that must be, I can't honestly say that I'm jealous.
Pressure, huh...?
Or stress.
Animation Number 181
Stress, huh...?
Well, since you're crawling at rock bottom and can't even imagine those really smart people, Araragi-kun,
you're just going to have to put in
more and more effort, then try harder.
That's why, from now on, every day, there will be tutoring at my house.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Maybe Kanbaru's house would be fine too, once in a while.
What does Kanbaru have to do with it?
I have to play with her a bit, too. I promised her that.
Araragi-kun, you'd want to play with Kanbaru too, right?
Well, yeah, she's an interesting person.
Oh yeah, about Kanbaru...
What about Kanbaru?
Why's she so erotic?
Erotic? Kanbaru?
Are you saying she's not?
Even Oshino seemed to recognize her as an erotic person rather than as an athletic person when I talked to him before.
Really? Maybe it only seems like that from a male's point of view.
She's just true to herself.
I see...
Personally, I can't overlook the fact that my cute junior is being given a label like "erotic."
Well, what are you going to do if you can't overlook it?
"What will I do?"
I'll warp the basis for your decision, the very foundation of your values.
Then Kanbaru will actually appear to be an innocent, pure-hearted girl.
Obscene line
Animation Number 201
S-Sto—
Animation Number 217
...and, that just about does it, Araragi-kun.
Just do whatever you want, Hitagi-san.
Next, commercials
Animation Number 126
parking
Silence
Animation Number 222
Ow!
Araragi-kun, wait here for a bit. I'll go on ahead alone and prepare.
Prepare for what?
Have a chat with Father or something.
Araragi-kun... was it?
Y-Yes. I'm Araragi Koyomi.
I see. Take good care of my daughter.
Just kidding.
Araragi-kun, you might have heard, but I'm the model businessman.
I have hardly any time to spend with Hitagi.
I see...
So this might not mean much, but it's been a long time since I've seen Hitagi having so much fun.
Silence / Disturbance
Animation Number 241
You've already heard about Hitagi's mother, right?
Yes.
And about Hitagi's condition too?
Well, that's not the only reason, and of course it's in no small part my fault for having prioritized my job,
but Hitagi closed her heart to others long ago.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Black Scene
Though recently, for the first time in a while, in a long while, Hitagi has asked me for favors.
She wanted me to let her help with my work.
And now this. Both times, you were involved.
I think you're quite something, Araragi-kun, to be able to change her.
It seems you think very highly of me, and I'm honored, but...
I think it was all coincidence.
Really? I heard that you had a hand in curing Hitagi of her condition, too.
Like I said, I don't think it was necessarily me.
Besides, Hitagi-san saved herself. I was just there to see her through it.
Father's line
Animation Number 260B
That's all you have to do.
More than anything else, I am thankful that you were there for her when she needed you.
I'm a failure as a father. I wasn't there when she needed me.
Well, even though I'm a failure of a father, I'm quite proud of my daughter. I trust her judgment.
If you're the man that she chose, then there's no argument.
Take good care of my daughter, Araragi-kun.
Father...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Araragi-kun.
Father, from here on it'll just be us young people. Thanks for driving us here.
We'll be back in about two hours,
so please go ahead and work until then.
Animation Number 274
Yeah.
Well then, Araragi-kun.
Thank you, Father.
Senjougahara, what's this place?
Animation Number 286
Have I ever once answered your question so far, Araragi?
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Hey, Senjougahara, how much longer are we going to walk like th—
Ouch!
Don't look up yet, Araragi-kun.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Close your eyes and lie down.
Hitagi's line
Animation Number 297
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
You can open your eyes now.
How is it, Araragi-kun?
Amazing, I seriously can't put it into words.
So you have poor vocabulary skills?
That's Deneb, Altair, Vega.
The famous Summer Triangle, okay?
From there, pan to the side, and that
area is Ophiuchus, the "snake-holder."
So Serpentis would be the stars lined up around there.
That remarkably bright one over there is Spica, so that area is Virgo.
Over there is Cancer, well, I guess it's a little hard to see...
Senjougahara Hitagi
Animation Number 300
HITAGI
hitagi
Animation Number 300
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That's everything.
What is?
Everything that I have, all of it.
Animation Number 301
The opportunity to tutor you,
a cute junior, a clumsy father,
and this starry sky...
These are the only things I have.
The only things I can give you, Araragi-kun, are things like these.
This is everything.
Everything...
Well, technically, I also have my insults and verbal assaults.
I don't need that.
Also, there's this thing called my body.
Do you not want that, either?
Well, that's...
But you know, I was almost violated by a perverted man, once.
Ah... yeah...
Honestly, I'm scared of doing what
that pervert tried to do to me with you.
Right now, I'm really afraid... of disliking you, Araragi-kun.
Right now, I'm afraid... of losing you.
Even though I can't say my life up until now was fortunate,
if I got your attention because I was so unfortunate, then I think it was okay, after all.
That's how hard I've fallen for you, Araragi-kun.
That's why, I'll make something come of it, no matter what. So... I want you to wait just a little.
That's why, at this point in time, out of everything I can give to you, Araragi-kun...
for now... this starry sky is the greatest.
I came here when I was a child; my father, my mother... and me.
It's my treasure.
Hey Araragi-kun, do you love me?
I love you.
I love you too, Araragi-kun.
Thank you.
Which parts about me do you like?
I like everything about you. There's nothing I don't like.
Is that so? I'm glad.
How about you? Which parts do you like about me?
That you're nice, you're cute, and you come to my rescue, like a prince, whenever I'm in trouble.
I'm happy.
Now that I think about it, since that pervert was only after my body, he didn't even try to take my lips.
That's why, Araragi-kun,
we're going to kiss.
No... that's not what I mean.
Could... could you... kiss me?
How... how about... we kiss?
Let's kiss, Araragi-kun.
So it ultimately comes down to that.
itsumo doori no aru hi no koto
Just like any other day
That's how today became a day to be celebrated...
kimi wa totsuzen tachiagari itta
you suddenly started to speak,
konya hoshi wo mi ni yukou
"Tonight, let's go look at the stars"
for us.
are ga DENEBU ARUTAIRU BEGA
That's Deneb, Altair, Vega
kimi wa yubisasu natsu no daisankaku
the summer triangle that you pointed out.
oboete
So remember
sora wo miru
to look at the sky.
yatto mitsuketa orihimesama
I finally found you, Altair,
dakedo doko darou hikoboshisama
though where are you, Vega?
kore ja hitoribocchi
This is loneliness.
makkura no sekai kara miageta
I looked up from the pitch-dark world.
yozora wa hoshi ga furu you de
The stars fell in the night sky, and
itsu kara darou
just when was it from?
kimi no koto wo
That I, who ran after you,
oikakeru watashi ga ita
was there.
douka onegai
Please heed my wish.
odorokanaide
Don't be surprised.
kiite yo
Listen
watashi no
to these feelings
kono omoi wo
of mine.
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
Bakemonogatari
Cat
Tsubasa Cat, Part Two
TO BE CONTINUED
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Karen, you said you do Karate, right?
Yeah! I do!
Aren't karate and café latte similar?
They are!
Just about as similar as chiropractics and plastic hand warmers, right?
They are! They're even more similar!
I wonder if they're related?
Possibly.
It'd be nice if they were.
Preview Quiz!
Quiz!
Isn't quiz similar to cream cheese?
They are!
Just about as similar as beef stew and a meat hot pot, right?
Next episode: Tsubasa Cat part three.
Next Time
Tsubasa Cat, Part Three
Isn't part three and Somo-san similar?
They are!