koko wo migi
Turn right here,
tsugi hidari
then take the next left
mou nicchi mo sacchi mo ikanakute komaru
nothing's working out. I'm so troubled!
migi hidari
Right, left, reft, light,
higi hidari
basu no mado kara teashi wo dasu na
Don't let your limbs outside the bus window!
soko hidari
Left there, then immediately take the right,
sugu migi e
mou docchi ga docchi demo kekkyoku onnaji
It doesn't matter which you take, the result will be the same.
hare nocchi kumori tokoro ni yori
Sunny but cloudy later in the day,
tokidoki ame mitai na koto dayo ne
Partly rainy in some places, it's like this, right?
yorimichi bakari shitetara
After I keep taking detours, before I knew it,
itsu no ma ni ka
hi ga kureteru
it's already the end of the day, with the end of the year coming.
toshi mo kureteru
tohouni kurechatteru
I'm all out of options to take!
onaka ga naku kara kaerou
Since my stomach is empty I'm going back,
massugu ouchi e kaerou
going back straight to my home.
kokoro ga mayou toki wa
When my heart wanders,
sono egao ga mejirushi
that smile is the guide.
te to te wo tsunaide kaerou
Take hand in hand and go home.
issho ni ouchi e kaerou
Let's go home together.
itsu datte soko ni ite
Always being there,
mitsukete kureru anata
you always find me.
toomawari demo
Even though it's a roundabout route,
toomawari ja nai
it isn't a roundabout route!