Putting that aside, Araragi-san.
What?
I'm hungry.
Animation Number 005A
Then let's go eat somewhere once Senjougahara comes back.
Do you have anything you like to eat?
I like any kind of food.
Your hands were also rather tasty.
My hands are not food.
You're just being humble. They really were tasty.
Speaking of which, you probably really did swallow some of my flesh and blood,
so I can't exactly take your words lightly.
- By the way, Hachikuji. Is it true
that you went to your mother's house?
It's true.
I'm not lying.
- I see ... ...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
Still,
"it had been quite some time,
so she became lost"...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
...I don't think that is the reason.
Since she ran into the snail,
even though this is not the place where it started...
No, wait...
Why did Hachikuji run into the snail?
Reason.
There was a reason why I was attacked by a vampire.
For Hanekawa's case and for Senjougahara's.
So, there should be a reason
for Hachikuji as well.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Say, this might sound like an oversimplification, but I take it your objective
wasn't to reach the destination by itself, you just wanted to meet
your mother, right?
- "Just" is a cruel word to use, but you're correct.
- Then why don't you ask her to come to you.
Look, even if you can't reach Tsunade-san's house, your mother is not confined there.
- It's impossible. Or more precisely, it's pointless.
That was Hachikuji's
immediate answer.
- If it were possible, I'd have done it long ago.
But it is impossible
Remaining/left-over
Ghost
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
- I can't even call my mother on the phone.
- Hmm.
- I can only visit my mother like this. Even if I knew
I can never reach her place.
Typeface used for images: HGP mincho B
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
Episode 5
Hachikuji, I don't quite understand why, but you want to see your mother, correct?
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I was under the belief that it's rather normal for children to want to see their mother. Am I wrong?
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Well, of course not, but...
You live with your parents, right? That's why you don't understand.
If you lived by yourself, I think you would want to see them, too.
Is that how it is?
From the way you've been speaking, I get the feeling that you don't really like your parents.
It's not like that. I just...
Up until middle school, I was a really good kid.
I didn't disobey my parents for any reason.
Dad
Animation Number 'none'
Thank you, mother, father.
Koyomi.
I was really grateful to them for raising me.
How nice.
But when I got to high school, I fell behind in my studies.
Naoetsu High School Textbook
Animation number 23
The monkey gave the persimmon
seed to the crab.
The crab gave the rice ball
to the monkey.
Sprout quickly, persimmon seed,
if you don't, I'll cut you with my claws.
Naoetsu High School Textbook
Animation number 23
Then the good-kid image that I had maintained took a complete turn.
I had this unspeakable, unpleasant kind of feeling.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Brother, you're
always like that!
Brother, you're always like that!
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Because of that, they said that's why no matter how much time passes, I'll never grow up.
Never growing up. Always just a child. Apparently.
A child? Then you're just like me.
I think it's a bit different than you, honestly.
They probably mean something along the line of,
"He's grown up on the outside, but inside he hasn't changed at all."
Feeler
But you know, Araragi-san, I'm considered quite mature amongst my classmates.
That's true. Your chest is pretty developed.
You touched it?! When did you touch it?!
When we were fighting.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
My first touch has been taken!
First touch?
Bee
To actually have a first touch before a first kiss!
Hachikuji Mayoi has turned into a pervert!
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Ah, that's right, Hachikuji-chan. I completely forgot.
I promised you that I'd give you some allowance, didn't I?
Please don't say that with such horrible timing!
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
There, there, there.
Araragi-san, you don't look even the least bit apologetic.
You should at least say something after touching a girl's delicate chest!
Thanks?
Animation Number
No, I'm asking you to apologize!
Speaking of which, it doesn't really matter, does it? It's not that big a deal.
They say that they'll get bigger if you rub them.
What?! You've been using that superstition as a shield
to constantly touch girls' breasts, haven't you?!
You're the worst.
Unfortunately, I've never had such an opportunity.
I see you're just a stupid virgin, aren't you?
How can you know, elementary school student?
Animation Number 51
That's dangerous! Seriously, it's dangerous!
I've been touched by a virgin! I've been contaminated!
It's the same no matter who touches you!
I'm beginning to lose my slight feeling of guilt!
Quarrel
I can't take it anymore! What are you, a rabid dog?!
Since it's like this, who cares about the first?! Who cares about a kiss?!
I'll rub your chest until you don't care about that anymore!
GROPE
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
There was a high school boy who was going to forcibly sexually harass an elementary school girl.
But... just this once, I don't want to believe that's me.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Five minutes later
Animation number 62
I'm sorry...
Wound
No,
I should be the one apologizing.
But Hachikuji, you sure know how to put up a fight.
It happens a lot in school. You put up a good fight, too.
Araragi
|
I used to always fight like that with my sister.
I suppose this sort of fight is over if one side apologizes...
What's wrong, Ararararagi-san?
This time there are two extra "ra"s.
Pardon me. I stuttered.
Ararararagi
|
Arararagi
Araragi
|
No, that was on purpose.
I st-stuttered.
It wasn't on purpose!?
I can't help it. Everyone misspeaks at some point.
Or are you saying that you haven't stuttered once since you were born?
Not exactly, but at least I don't stutter when saying someone else's name.
Then, please say "nanamumi nanamome namamamamo" three times.
Namamumi
Namamome
Namamamamo
Animation Number 78
You didn't even say it right.
Namamome is so obscene!
Animation Number 79B
Namamome
Bashful
You said it, not me.
Namamamamo is obscene, too!
Animation Number 80B
Namamamamo
Bashful
How is that obscene? I don't really get it...
Speaking of which, won't saying it intentionally be more difficult?
Namamamamo.
Namamamamo
Namamamamo!
Mitsuo (uso)
Stuttering and
stuttering makes for
a hurried man.
Then may I know what happened, Araragi-san?
Nothing much.
I just thought of how I should apologize to my sister, and I got a bit depressed.
Having to apologize...
Don't tell me you touched her breasts?
Who would touch their own sister's breasts?
When I left the house today, I sort of had a quarrel with my sister.
I used to fight constantly with my mother and father, too.
Not physically, though.
Only verbally.
As an only daughter, it's not really my place to say this, but...
They looked like a happy couple on the surface.
But I've never seen them get along...
They were constantly fighting.
You love your mother, don't you?
Yes, I love her.
Of course, I love my father as well.
Even though my father and mother fought constantly and eventually split up, I still love them both.
I see.
That's why, because of that, I'm feeling uneasy.
My father seems to hate my mother a lot.
Because of that, he doesn't let me see her.
I wonder, if this continues, will I forget my mother someday?
If I can never see her again, will I stop loving her someday?
I'm so uneasy...
I smell another woman.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
O-Oh, Senjougahara.
This scent of shampoo...
It belongs to Hanekawa-san, doesn't it?
You can tell?
To a certain extent.
You can also think of it as using the shape of the waist to differentiate women.
I don't remember displaying such special abilities.
You can't do it?
Don't react like it's not ordinary!
You have an outstanding pelvic stance. It looks rather suitable for childbirth,
so I think you'll be able to give birth to a healthy baby.
Didn't you say that to me recently?
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Those were the words of some other pervert out there!
Then, Hanekawa-san came, didn't she?
Yeah, she came.
She already went home, though.
She merely passed by.
You must have heard the details from Oshino-san, right, Senjougahara?
Araragi-kun, it seems that I have to apologize to you.
Oshino-san told me I should.
What could you possibly need to apologize for?
Even if there's only one actual truth, you can have two truths from two different perspectives.
A method to determine which truth is true doesn't actually exist.
There's no real method of proving your truth in this world.
But believing that you're wrong for that reason is also wrong.
He talks as if he can see right through you.
I hate that.
What the hell are you saying?
No, not you, but rather Oshino.
What you said doesn't seem to have any connection with the current situation.
The way to get released from the snail, the lost cow, is apparently rather simple.
You get lost because you follow the snail, so if you go away from it, you won't be lost.
You get lost because you follow it?
In the case of the snail, it seems that the human that becomes its target is led astray.
That's why you only need to get away from the snail.
No, not me, right? Hachikuji does.
But if it's like that, don't you find it weird?
She didn't follow the snail on her own.
There's no way she'd want that.
That's why I need to apologize to you, Araragi-kun.
But, even so, I hope you'll let me explain.
I didn't have any bad intentions.
Besides, it wasn't on purpose.
I thought for certain that I had made a mistake.
Senjougahara...
Well, think about it.
For over two years, I have not been normal.
If something happened, I would think that it was my fault.
It can't be helped.
Hey, Senjougahara...
Hachikuji-chan, is it?
Basically, Araragi-kun...
You felt bad on Mother's Day, fought with your sister, didn't want to go back home...
That girl...
I can't see her.
It was just about 10 years ago.
At a certain place, a husband and wife walked toward the end of marriage.
It was decided that their only daughter would go with the father.
No matter what one's memories are, they get worn down.
No matter what one's memories are, they deteriorate.
With the flow of time, the only daughter was shocked.
She no longer remembered her mother's face.
For you
About you
With you
Even if she looked at her mother's photos,
she couldn't tell if that was really her own mother anymore.
Bakemonogatari
Story two
Because she is the mother
That's why the only daughter decided to go see her mother on the Mother's Day of that year.
Maybe you
were hated?
Don't you think
you were forgotten?
Weren't you
a bother for here?
Because she is the mother
After all, I'm her only daughter
After all, I'm her
For you
About you
With you
After all, I'm her only daughter
After all, I'm her
Still Still Still Still Still Still Still
But she did not reach her mother's home.
even so even so even so
even so even so even so even so
mother I mother I mother I mother I mother I mother I mother I
I wonder why. Why?
love you so much love you so much love you so much love
love you so much love you so much love you so much love you so much love you so much
Really, why was that?
if possible, you too if possible, you too if possible, you too if possible, you too if possible, you too if possible, you too
The traffic light was clearly green.
please love me back please love me back please love me back please love me back please love me back please love me back
That only daughter is me.
From then on, were you always lost?
A person who cannot reach her destination will hinder another person's way home.
Going around in circles.
Basically, Hachikuji.
But are you sure you can't see Hachikuji?
No, I can't even hear her voice.
But you were acting so naturally...
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
I can't see that sort of thing.
The only thing I see is a person talking to himself.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
The last thing I saw was Araragi-kun going crazy.
I totally didn't understand what you were doing.
If it's like that, you only need to tell me...
Like I said, there's no way I could just say it.
It's impossible for me to just say it.
If such a thing happened... If the thing that you could see, I couldn't...
Then I would normally think that it's me that has a problem.
That's right.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Senjougahara doesn't want to feel that something is wrong with her again.
She doesn't want to feel that she became abnormal once again...
She doesn't want me to feel that way either...
That's why she pretended to be able to see Hachikuji.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Animation Number 181
The one who ran into the snail... was me?
Animation Number 182
Araragi-kun, Oshino-san said that the criteria for meeting the lost cow is the desire not to return home.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
But everyone thinks that sometimes.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Every family has their problems, no matter who they are.
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
She's the same.
Friction and strain in her family...
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
But because of that, Araragi-kun, dealing with the lost cow is very simple.
I said from the start that as long as you stop following it and distance yourself, it'll be okay.
That's all you need to do...
"It's a strange thing that isn't very evil or strong."
"It isn't really a dangerous threat in the first place." That's what he said.
That's why...
Animation Number 188
So.
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
That's why...?
Animation Number 188
So?
Then what, Senjougahara?
What I mean is how to get this girl-
How to get Hachikuji to her mother's place.
Animation Number 193B
Separation
Animation Number 193C
Divorce
Animation Number 193D
Bereavement
Animation Number 194
Do you understand, Araragi-kun?
This child does not exist there.
She does not exist there, nor does she exist anywhere.
Hachikuji. The child called Hachikuji Mayoi-chan...
is already dead.
That's why this child is not being possessed by something, but is that something itself.
So what?
A-Araragi-san, it hurts.
Araragi-san, everything is exactly as Senjougahara-san said.
I... I'm...
Red Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Shut up!
You may not have heard it, Senjougahara.
This girl said some really outrageous things to me and Hanekawa from the start.
Please don't speak to me. I hate you.
Mayoi Hachikuji
Class 5-3
Animation number 203B
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Do you understand, Senjougahara?
Because she doesn't want anyone to follow her, that's why she says such things to everyone she meets.
Can you understand that?!
I totally don't understand, but even so, when I was missing and when I was all alone,
the feeling of having the need to say such things...
You and I... haven't we experienced the same thing, just in a different way?!
Even though you can't see her, hear her voice, or even smell her...
Even so... That's why...
It's my duty to bring her safely to her mother's side.
I knew you would say that.
I finally understand you, Araragi-kun.
When you found out about my problem,
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
you took the initiative to speak to me on that day.
Why is that so?
Did you perhaps offer help solely because it was me?
But that wasn't the case.
That wasn't the case.
It was purely...
because you'll save anyone, right?
Say, Araragi...
Animation number 221D
Save them... it's nothing that amazing. You're exaggerating.
But two years after encountering that strange thing, even though many people realized my problem...
the only person like you was you.
Well, sure. I'm just me.
That's right. Of course.
Mayoi Hachikuji
Animation number 221D
This is the last message Oshino-san left, Araragi-kun.
"Just this once, I'll teach you a trick that can be of use."
Trick?
Okay, let's go.
Go? Where to?
To Tsunade-san's house, of course.
And, Araragi-kun...
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
What?
Congratulations.
The lost cow, as an anomaly, is a ghost-type.
A
Under construction
Halted
Due to this, it can't store new
information-oriented memories.
Information-oriented memories are, basically, knowledge.
We're here.
Huh?
Animation Number 243
It's understandable for a person like me who has no geographic knowledge at all.
But for Senjougahara, who can't even see the snail, to be lost...
Gas
Still, something you don't know will still be unknown.
No. Even if you know, you will be unable to react.
But this is...
A
Rezoning Laws
Chapter one - General rules
(Article 1 - Article 3.4)
Chapter two - Contractors
Section one - Individual contractors
(Article 4 - Article 13)
Section two - Land rezoning board
Clause one - Establishment
(Article 14 - Article 24)
Clause two - Management
(Article 25 - Article 44)
Clause three - Dissolution and joining
(Article 45 - Article 51)
Section three - Rezoning companies
(Article 51.2 - Article 51.3)
Section four - Administrative divisions and cities
(Article 52 - Article 65)
Section five - Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport (MLIT)
(Article 66 - Article 71)
Section six - Urban Renaissance Agency
(Article 71.2 - Article 71.6)
Chapter three - Land rezoning projects
Clause one - General rules
(Article 72 - Article 85.4)
Clause two - Land replotting schedule
(Article 86 - Article 97)
Clause three - Provisional replotting
(Article 98 - Article 102)
Clause four - Notice of replotting
(Article 103 - Article 108)
Clause five - Price reduction compensation grants
(Article 109)
Clause six - Settlement.
(Article 110 - Article 112)
Clause seven - Laws in Relation to Rights
(Article 113 - Article 117)
Clause eight - Residence construction for allocated residential areas
(Article 117.2)
Clause nine - MLIT skilled laborer examination
(Article 117.3 - Article 117.19)
Chapter four - Charging and expenses
(Article 118 - Article 121)
Chapter five - Supervision.
(Article 122 - Article 127.2)
Chapter six - Miscellaneous rules
(Article 128 - Article 136.4)
Chapter seven - Penal regulations.
(Article 137 - Article 139)
For instance, take the district map.
If you only choose the newly-built routes, the lost cow will be unable to react.
After an hour going somewhere that shouldn't even take ten minutes,
we finally reached the destination.
But...
PRIVATE
private land - entry prohibited
PRIVATE LAND
Development and Construction Union
It was just an empty area.
Animation number 263
Senjougahara, are you sure this is the place?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
I don't believe it...
Sob.
Animation Number 266
I'm home!
You've done well, Araragi-kun.
You were perhaps a tiny bit cool.
This time it's all thanks to you, though.
Even so, that's not what I mean, you know.
By the way, Araragi-kun.
You have not given me an answer yet.
What will you do?
No, I think you might have misunderstood something.
Look, didn't you mention something about repaying me?
That was only an excuse.
I merely wanted you to confess on your own.
But don't worry.
I don't really feel that I owe you something big.
Because you love to help others.
But even if the person that was being helped was not me...
Even if, from the side, I watched you help Hanekawa-san or the others...
I would still have developed special feelings for you.
Well, though I seem to have said this before...
If you insist, I find talking to you to be fun. That's all.
But we haven't really talked that much, have we?
I suppose.
That's why I hope to speak more with you.
How do I put it...?
Maybe it's because I've taken a liking to you. That's why I want to try hard, or something like that anyway.
I see...
All right, well how about you think of it like this?
Unfortunately, a psychotic virgin,
starved for love and likely to fall for anyone who would be a little nice to her, has set her eyes on you.
I see.
You are really unlucky.
Blame it on your habitual actions.
If you are to say something stupid like, "Give me a bit of time to consider,"
I will despise you, Araragi-kun.
Don't let a girl feel shameful.
I get it.
At this point in time, I feel that I'm really horrible.
But is it all right if I offer one condition?
Not really a condition... It's more like a promise.
A promise? What is it?
Senjougahara, pretending to see things that you actually can't...
Or pretending not to be able to see something you really can...
No more of that, from now on.
If our views clash, then let us properly talk about it.
Promise me.
A simple request.
Then let's get going. It's already getting dark.
Araragi-kun, could you clearly say it for me?
Say it?
Because I hate unclear relationships.
You mean that?
I hope this will be popular.
Huh?
"Senjougahara fascination."
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
Namishiro park
Koyomi, it's morning!
You have to wake up!
That's Deneb, Altair, Vega
I promised that on Mother's Day next year, I will definitely not take a single step from home.
the summer triangle that you pointed out.
So remember
You should definitely be at home on Mother's Day next year. From: your sisters.
I absolutely won't go out.
I will stay home no matter what.
Koyomi.
It may be a good thing.
to look at the sky.
Mom said we'll be washing the bedsheets today!
I finally found you, Altair,
She said that she can only start washing when you wake up!
though where are you, Vega?
When morning came, my sisters seemed to have calmed down.
This is loneliness.
I looked up from the pitch-dark world.
Bi
Wheel
Animation Number 335B
The stars fell in the night sky, and
Black Scene
Animation Number 'none'
just when was it from?
Aren't you...?
Aragi-san.
Aragi-san
Animation Number 343B
That I, who ran after you,
You left out a "ra" this time.
Excuse me. I stuttered.
was there.
What are you doing?
Well, how do I put it...?
Please heed my wish.
Um... I have been promoted from an earthbound spirit into a wandering spirit.
Don't be surprised.
Listen
Which means I was promoted two ranks.
to these feelings
Umm, Araragi-san...
I will probably be around here for the time being.
of mine.
Bakemonogatari
Snail
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
Bakemonogatari
Snail
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
Bakemonogatari
Snail
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
Bakemonogatari
Snail
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
Bakemonogatari
Snail
Mayoi Snail, Part Three
CONTINUED NEXT TIME
If you see me, please talk to me.
It was just an empty area.
Animation number 263
I'm Karen.
I'm Tsukihi.
An octopus spits ink.
Spits, huh?
There's also a fish that spits ink.
Spit-Spit!
You might think that's all.
Eh? Don't tell me they inhale ink!
Ehh.. it's not like that.
Well, which is it?
You know... there is a fish which spits ink!
Oh, it's Akanagana, right?
How do you know that?!
I know of most black things!
Time for today's baseball quiz!
Quiz!
You are a baseball pitcher.
The pitcher raises his hands above his head and pitches.
But the first, second, and even the third and fourth pitch are all fouled off straight pitches!
No control!
Now for the question!
Your fourth pitch was...
Who would know that?
It couldn't be a straight...
Next time, Suruga Monkey Part 1.
Next Time
Suruga Monkey, Part One
It was a question of straight pitch victory or defeat!
It wasn't clever.